[{"id":823,"question":"BASH stands for:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Bourne Again SHell","answer_b":"BAsic SHell","answer_c":"Basic Async SHell","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":662,"question":"Which command can give first found difference between two file after comparing?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"diff","answer_b":"cmp","answer_c":"Common","answer_d":"stat","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":681,"question":"Who designed the Linux OS?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Linus Torvalds","answer_b":"Steve Jobs","answer_c":"Steve Wozniak","answer_d":"Steve Linus","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":680,"question":"How can you display the top 10 number of lines of a file?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"head \u2212n 10 file.txt","answer_b":"head -f 10 file.txt","answer_c":"head --display-only 10 file.txt","answer_d":"head -show 10 file.txt","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"},{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1071,"question":"From which file does the command `free` takes it's information","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"\/proc\/meminfo","answer_b":"\/proc\/freemem","answer_c":"\/proc\/memfree","answer_d":"\/dev\/meminfo","answer_e":"\/dev\/freemem","answer_f":"\/dev\/memfree"},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":693,"question":"What are the respective octal value for the permission bits?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"4, 2 & 1 respectively for r, w & x.","answer_b":"4, 2 & 1 respectively for w, r & x.","answer_c":"4, 2 & 1 respectively for x, w & x.","answer_d":"4, 2 & 1 respectively for r, x & w.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"},{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":654,"question":"Which option can be used with \u2018rm\u2019 command to prompt for file removal?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"-ask","answer_b":"-i","answer_c":"-c","answer_d":"-n","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":711,"question":"Are arrays supported in shell scripts?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":"Yes but only under certain conditions","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"},{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":691,"question":"Which operator can be used to throw a process into background?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"&","answer_b":"&&","answer_c":"|","answer_d":"||","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":737,"question":"How to delete a pod in Kubernetes using the type and name specified in pod.json?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl delete .\/pod.json","answer_b":"kubectl delete -f .\/pod.json","answer_c":"kubectl remove -f .\/pod.json","answer_d":"kubectl remove .\/pod.json","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"}]